[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Hi, everybody.
&gt;&gt; 大家好
My name is Pedraum Pardehpoosh.
我是Pedraum Pardehpoosh
I run Product for the App Store.
主要负责 App Store 产品业务
Thanks for joining us today.
感谢大家今天的到来
We've brought a few people
可能今天在座的有一些人
together that normally don't get
平时不太爱
out of the office.
出办公室
So this is going to be a session
所以今天的这场演讲
that might be a little different
可能和之前的那些
than what you're used to here.
有所不同
It's a deeper look into the App
这次将会更加深层次地探讨 App Store
And I'm thrilled that you joined
我非常高兴各位
us.
来到这里
You heard about the App Store
大家应该都听说了
from Phil on Monday at the
周一 Phil 在主题演讲中
keynote.
提到了 App Store
And the staggering numbers that
而这些惊人的数字
demonstrate what a smash hit
都表明
it's been.
它有多成功
But today we're going to spend a
但今天我们要
little time giving you an
花一点时间来
overview of the App Store.
了解 App Store 概览
Go a little deeper.
更进一步
We'll look at the design
探索设计
philosophy that went into the
哲学
"why" we did it.
即我们“为何”这样做
And we'll go a little deeper
也将进一步探索
into our emphasis on editorial.
我们对编辑的重视
Finally, we'll bring it all back
最后我们会
and talk about the implications
探讨一下这些对你们有什么影响
to you, the developers that
诸位都是应用
bring it to life.
的开发者
Let's get started.
我们开始吧
Who remembers this?
谁还记得这个
[ Cheering and Applause ]
[欢呼声掌声]
It's the original App Store, the
这是最初的 App Store
OG.
OG
It had been launched in July of
推出于 2008 年 7 月
2008 with 500 apps.
内含 500 个 App
And this is a little inside
这里还有个内部小故事
There were some prominent
当时
executives at the company that
公司有些高层
didn't think we'd have more than
认为我们永远不会
a thousand apps in the App Store
在 App Store 中有超过 1000 个 App
ever.
布局和陈列
the store have largely remained
基本没有太大变动
the same.
我们做过更改
there, but overall it's the same
但大体还是一样的
Tweaks have been made.
做了些微小的改进
Well, nine years later there are
但9年后的今天
2.2 million apps in the store.
App Store 里有 220 万个 App
And it's transformed the way
改变了
software is bought and
购买和分发软件的方式
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
It's hard to imagine a time
很难想象
before Apps.
App 出现之前的世界
It's permeated every facet of
它已经渗透进我们生活的方方面面
our lives from the way we travel
从旅游出行
to the way we find love.
到发现爱情
[ Laughter ]
[笑声]
And they've affected entire
它们也影响了
industries as well.
整个产业
From airline travel to
从航旅
healthcare to gaming.
到医疗保健再到游戏
As well as the way we play
以及我们玩游戏的方式
games.
在大屏幕上大家能看到
Hong Kong playing Pokemon Go on
在周一的香港人们玩着 Pokemon Go
And I think it's just bonkers.
我觉得这简直有病
I love it.
但我喜欢
Well at this point in the
在这个 App Store 的
history of the App Store, we
历史节点上
pause to consider how we can
我们停下来
make it even better.
思考如何做到更好
How we could redesign it from
如何从头开始
the ground up.
重新设计
And as we began doing that, we
而当我们开始做时
realized it could serve a few
我们意识到可以做到以下几点
One, we thought how can we give
首先如何吸引
customers a reason to come back
回头客
every day?
让 App Store 成为
want to visit on a daily basis?
用户每天都想访问的地方
Second, we thought this was a
其次我们认为现在是
perfect time to double down on
完美的时刻
the editorial curation that's
来让自 App Store 成立以来
distinguished the App Store
就十分优秀的
since its inception.
编辑策展更加优秀
And finally, we wanted to
再次我们想
reflect the significance the
反映出
games play in the App Store and
App Store 中游戏的意义
give both games and apps a
给予游戏和应用
clearer focus.
更为清晰的重点
At this stage, we began an
在这一阶段我们开始了一段
intense journey of redesigning
认真严肃的旅程重新设计
the store from the ground up.
App Store 从头开始
To tell you more about the
为了让大家对这一过程了解更多
process, I'm thrilled to hand it
我很高兴
over to Monika Gromek who led
欢迎Monika Gromek 上台
these design efforts.
她是设计团队的领导
Monika.
Monika
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thanks Pedraum, for letting
&gt;&gt; 感谢Pedraum
me out of the office once in a
让我偶尔从办公室出来
while.
透透气
And thank you all for coming to
也感谢各位
this session.
莅临现场
My name is Monika Gromek and I
我是Monika Gromek
lead the App Store design team
带领 Apple 的 App Store 设计团队
This redesign of the App Store
重新设计App Store
is so significant that we felt
如此重要以至于我们认为
it deserved a session dedicated
它值得一场
just to this one topic.
专场会议
And hopefully by the end of it
希望在会议结束时
you'll be much more familiar
大家会对
with the changes that we're
我们做出的改变
making and all the new features
和介绍的新特色
that we're introducing.
更加熟悉
I am going to cover the major
我将会讲到重新设计
parts of the redesign.
的大部分内容
But I would like start with our
但我想以
goals and the design process.
我们的目标和设计过程来开场
As Pedraum mentioned, the App
正如Pedraum提到的
Store launched nine years ago.
App Store 发布于9年前
And it's so hard to believe that
很难相信
so much time has passed.
已经过了这么久
And we are incredibly proud of
我们也对它现在的样子
what it has become.
感到十分骄傲
And mostly, thanks to all of you
但最重要的是感谢大家
and the amazing apps and games
带来的应用和游戏
that you create every day.
每天都有新惊喜
So why the redesign?
所以为什么要重新设计呢
Well, it was time for us to take
因为是时候
a long, hard look at the current
认真审视现在的 App Store
store and acknowledge its
并承认它仍有局限了
limitations, as none of us could
毕竟我们无人能够
have predicted its tremendous
预测它的迅猛成长
So just like every other app and
所以就像 App Store 中每一位
game creator on the App Store,
应用和游戏开发者一样
we asked ourselves two
我们自问两个问题
questions: What are our goals
我们现在的目标是什么
And how does the current design
现有设计如何支持
support them?
我们的目标
For the new store, we touched
在新的 App Store 中
every single view and thought
我们触及所有观点
hard about the structure of the
并对应用的结构进行了深入思索
Believe me, there were a lot of
相信我当时我们有
options on the table.
不少选择
We applied lessons from other
我们吸取了 Apple 在其他方面
redesigns at Apple, but the
重新设计的经验
final design is unique to the
但是最终设计对于 App Store 而言
App Store.
是独一无二的
The end result is a new sense of
最终形成了一种带有清透且简约感觉的
clarity, a general
应用
simplification of the app, and a
以及
fresh take on editorial.
具有清新视角的编辑内容
The new style of typography
全新的排版风格
helps establish hierarchy on the
有助于打造页面层次结构
pages and a sense of space.
和空间感
It guides people throughout
引领人们
their journey.
探索发现
We've also removed extra layers
同时我们也移除了多余的
of UIs such as toggles to help
用户界面层比如切换层
with the overall experience in
来提升 App Store 的总体使用体验
Let's take a look at our
我们来看一下
redesign goals.
重新设计目标
As you can see, these are
正如大家所见
exactly the same as the ones you
和几分钟前各位听到的
heard a few minutes ago.
目标完全相同
This alignment of goals helped
这种目标一致性有助于
us create a product that's
我们创造
integrated, fluid and also
协调流畅而又美丽的产品
We did add one goal from the
但就设计层面而言
design side.
我们增加了一个目标
And that is clarity and
即清透
simplification.
简化
And it's probably the most
而且这可能是
important goal.
最重要的目标了
And I will expand on it later.
稍后我会扩展开来讲
I want to start by talking about
我想先讲讲
the App Store as a daily
让 App Store 成为每日访问
destination and the editorial
站点和
voice on the App Store, as the
App Store 中编辑的看法
two goals are very closely
鉴于这两大目标高度相关
To do that, I want to bring up
那么我就要提到
the Today view.
Today 视图
You saw it in the Monday
各位在周一的主题演讲中已经见到它了
But let's take a closer look.
但让我们更进一步谈谈它
It all starts with the Today
它始于 Today
tab.
标签
This is our new home for the App
这里是 App Store 的新家
This is where we can share our
在这里我们能分享
passion for apps and games and
对应用和游戏的热情
celebrate all of you, the
同时赞扬所有开发者
This is where you can come and
在这里你能
learn our editorial perspective
从编辑视角
on the world of apps and games.
了解应用和游戏的世界
This view is a dynamic,
这一视图作为充满活力
ever-changing platform that
日新月异的平台
allows us to feature your
让我们能够以
products in a very different
你们的产品作为主要特色
light than ever before.
并且用全新的方式来加以主推
We designed it as a series of
我们设计了一系列卡片
cards that update daily and
每日更新
allow us to celebrate your apps
这样我们就可以
and games by telling stories.
用讲故事的方式来赞美这些应用和游戏
We've had this desire to tell
我们想这样做
stories for a long time now but
已经很久了
haven't been able to do it in a
但一直没能找到
meaningful and engaging way.
这样迷人而意义非凡的方式
But this is all changing now
但现在有了 Today 标签的帮助
with the Today tab.
我们终于可以了
What you see here is our video
现在看到的视频卡片
We can highlight your app and
我们能突出应用和
game previews and our
游戏预览
editorially-created videos.
以及编辑制作的视频
We will be providing helpful
我们会提供有用的
tips and tricks as seen in this
提示和技巧
example for VSCO.
就像现在 VSCO 样例中看到的这样
And we will be nominating an App
我们还会提名
of the Day and a Game of the
每日应用和每日游戏
And we will also be sharing our
同时也将展示
curated collections.
策展合辑
Some of you might be familiar
可能在座有些人对
with our collections, as we've
合辑比较熟悉
been creating them for years,
因为几年来我们一直在创建合辑
but haven't had a way to
但未能找到一种
highlight them in a predictable
在用户界面中以可预测方式
way in our UI.
突出它们的操作
But again, this is different now
但现在
with the Today tab and these
有了 Today 标签和上述卡片
cards.
我们能做到了
We spent a lot of time thinking
我们花了很多时间思考
about how to best showcase your
如何在这一视图中
apps and games in this view.
最好地展示应用和游戏
It was important to us that it
视觉美观
looked beautiful, so we spent a
对我们十分重要
lot of time thinking about every
所以我们思索良久
single detail.
考虑每个细节
Everything kept us up at night
熬夜奋战
for months, be it typography,
数月之久从排版
layout, transitions and
布局转换
animations.
到动画
Each card is an entry point for
每一张卡片都是一个入口
a deeper discovery.
去探索更深远的世界
And we also hope to give you
我们也希望能提供
some context into why you should
吸引你点进来探索这个故事
tap in and check out that story.
的一些内容
At any given point we will give
在任何时候我们都会提供
you up to seven days' worth of
最多七天的
content.
内容
So if you miss a day or two, you
如果你错过了一天两天
can come back and find it later.
你可以稍后回来再看
Just look for the date markers.
寻找日期标记就好
We also included animations on
我们也为一些卡片
some of these cards to make them
添加了动画
come to life.
让它们栩栩如生
You've already seen the
您已经看过了
auto-playing video.
自动播放视频
But we hope to bring more
但我们希望能为
movement into this view.
这一视图带来更多动感
Twelve cards will be ready for
12张卡片即将就绪
launch.
准备发布
We needed a variety to keep
我们需要多样化
things interesting.
来保持趣味性
But also to be able to tell
但同时也需要
diverse type of stories.
能够讲述不同类型的故事
And each one of these cards
这组卡片中的每一张
allows us to tell a story in a
都能以不同的方式
different way.
讲述一个故事
It was also important that these
同样重要的是
cards look good together and
这些卡片做为一个整体也很美观
work as a system.
并且能作为一个系统运作起来
The order in which they appear
它们出现的顺序
might be different, so what you
可能会有不同
see one day might be very
所以今天看到的
different from what you will see
和明天看到的
tomorrow, for example.
可能就会有很大差异
But, there's a lot of thought
但是也有
that goes into creating these
很多考量
every single day around the
在全世界范围内每天变换出现
We haven't done this before.
之前我们从没有做过这些
And believe me, it keeps things
相信我这样才能保持趣味性
interesting, even at Apple.
即便在苹果也是如此
I do want to share one other
我还想分享关于
thing about the cards, which is
卡片的另一个故事
personally important to me.
对我个人来说十分重要
That this view is relevant world
即这一视图与全世界相关联
So all this content will be
所以所有内容
localized and culturally aware
都会本地化
in all our territories.
并适应当地文化
Let's take a closer look at one
让我们更进一步
of these stories.
看一看其中一个故事
It focuses on the fact that
它的关注点在于
behind every app there is a
在每一个应用背后
story of who made it, what
都有一个故事
motivated them, and how it was
讲述了创造者是谁受什么启发
made.
如何做出这个应用
It celebrates you and your apps
这些故事正是对各位开发者和你们的
and games.
应用和游戏的赞美
Let's dive in.
我们来看看吧
The transition into this story
进入故事的过程
is smooth and fluid.
平滑而流畅
And it's also easy to go back
返回 Today 视图
out to the Today view.
也十分容易
Simply tap on the X button or
只需轻点 X 按钮
swipe down on the article.
或向下滑动文章
The stories are engaging and
故事既迷人
informative.
又提供了大量信息
Smokey, who leads our editorial
Smokey 编辑团队的负责人
team, will come on stage in a
将稍后上台
bit and talk to you about it in
为大家讲述
more detail.
更多细节
But I want to highlight a few
但我想从设计层面
elements of these stories from
突出故事中的
the design perspective.
一些元素
We're letting the elements of
我们让这些故事中的元素
the stories define the space,
定义空间
allowing them to breathe and
让它们呼吸
convey our perspective.
并传达我们的看法
The videos let us engage with
而视频则让我们
the viewer like we've never been
和观看者互动
able to do before.
就像之前从未有过一样
And each story is a series of
每个故事都是一系列
modules defined by our design
由设计团队和编辑团队
and editorial teams.
定义的模块
We also hope that you will share
我们也希望你们能
these stories with one another
与彼此分享这些故事
and enjoy them as much as we do.
并和我们一样乐在其中
The modules allow for
这些模块
flexibility in terms of how
在如何构建故事方面
these stories are built.
表现得十分灵活
But they also keep things
但同时它们也
consistent from the design side.
在设计层面保持一致
So we have this common language
所以我们有共同的语言
that ties them all together,
来将它们联系在一起
making it easier for people to
让人们更容易
experience that content.
体验故事的内容
It's also worth mentioning that
同样值得一提的是
for the first time ever this
这是第一次
editorial content will be
编辑内容可以
searchable.
被搜索到
We've actually never had that in
这项功能在
the App Store.
App Store 中从未有过
And we are incredibly excited
对于这一点我们感到
about this.
兴奋不已
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
Absolutely.
就是这样
So if you miss a day, or if you
如果你错过了一天或是
miss some of this content, be it
错过了一部分内容
in the Today tab or any other
无论是在 Today 标签下
place in the App Store, you can
还是在 App Store 的其他位置
simply search for it later.
你都可以稍后搜索到它
It will be featured on the
同时
product page as well for that
该应用或游戏也将在
app or game.
产品页面上被予以推荐
And of course, the Today tab
当然 Today 标签
will be part of this App Store
也会作为 App Store 的一部分
on the iPad.
出现在 iPad 上
And that is the Today view.
这就是 Today 视图
We're incredibly excited about
我们对
how it looks and how it works.
它的外观和功能兴奋不已
But more importantly, about the
但更重要的是
type of stories it will allow us
它能让我们向你们
to tell you every single day.
每天讲述的故事
Let's talk about games next.
下面我们来聊聊游戏
Games have been always a huge
游戏一直以来都是
part of the App Store.
App Store 中的重头戏
But up to this point always
但到目前为止
mixed with apps throughout our
游戏和应用在
editorial and charts.
编辑和排行中都是混在一起的
Because of their importance and
由于游戏的重要性
success, we're dedicating a home
和成功度我们单独
just for games in the App Store.
在 App Store 中为游戏创建了一个家
And that is the new Games tab.
也就是新的游戏标签
It is more than a tab.
它可不仅仅是个标签
We're striving to create the
我们致力于打造
best, world's best game store.
全世界最好的游戏商店
Full of amazing content that
内容精彩纷呈
people are going to love.
让玩家爱不释手
The top of the page allows for
页面顶端
space for more stories to be
为讲述更多游戏
dedicated just to games or new
或新发布的故事
releases.
留出空间
And with more focus on videos,
随着视频获得更多关注
people will be able to discover
人们将能
games much more quickly and
更快地探索游戏
engage with them almost
几乎实现了即时互动
The split between apps and games
游戏和应用的分家
also allowed us to make charts
也让我们有效提升了 App Store
much more relevant in the App
排行榜的相关度
So, the charts that you're
所以现在各位
seeing are specifically
看到的排行榜
dedicated to games.
是仅限于游戏的榜单
And the same is true for apps.
对于应用也是一样
They will not be mixed in.
二者不会再混在一起
We think this will actually make
我们认为这样会
it a lot easier to find what's
更容易找到
popular on the App Store.
App Store 中的流行内容
The same is true of categories.
对于类别也是如此
As some of you may know, games
可能在座有人知道
was just one of the categories
游戏只是先前商店中的
in the previous store.
一个类别
Unfortunately, what it meant is
不幸的是这意味着
that all the subcategories were
所有子类别
harder to find and all that
和隐藏内容
content was hidden.
更难找到
But creating a tab dedicated for
但为游戏专门建立一个标签
games, we can take all those
我们就可以
categories and put them on the
把所有类别放到
top level, making browsing by
页面顶端
categories a lot easier and that
这样按类别浏览就容易许多
content a lot easier to find.
内容也更容易找到
Throughout the App Store will
自始至终 App Store 都会
also be providing more context
为任一应用或游戏
for any particular app or game.
提供更多内容
The App Store is no longer just
App Store 已经不只是
app icons.
应用图标的集合了
We want to help people find what
我们想帮人们找到
they're looking for and make the
他们所寻找的
right download choices.
并帮助他们做出正确的下载选择
The context can come from your
内容可以来自
subtitles that you will be
你们为应用提供的
providing for your apps.
副标题
And these subtitles are as
而现在副标题就和
important as your app names
应用的名字
today.
一样重要
And again, it's to provide
因为是向用户提供
people with more information
关于你们应用和游戏
about your app and game.
的更多信息
The context can also come from
内容页可以出自
the editorial team.
编辑团队之手
And you will see more and more
在未来大家将看到更多内容
of it throughout the App Store.
出现在 App Store 中
And that is the new Games tab.
这就是新的游戏标签
We're incredibly excited about
能够为游戏单独建立了一个家
having a dedicated home for
我们为此兴奋不已
Before we move on, I just wanted
但在我继续讲下去之前
to highlight a small but playful
我想突出一下
detail about the Games tab.
游戏标签这里一个小而有趣的细节
Icon. The shape of the rocket is
这个图标火箭形状
actually based on the leaf from
来源于 Apple 徽标
the Apple logo.
上的叶子
We thought some of you might
我们想着可能在座的一些人
find it interesting.
会觉得挺好玩
In addition to the Games tab,
除了游戏标签
we're also creating a new home
我们还给应用建了
for apps.
一个家
All the amazing content that you
所有
saw for the Games tab will also
在游戏标签下能够看到的内容
be available in the Apps tab.
在 App 标签下同样能够看到
From the design perspective
从设计角度来看
there was always this tension
在应用和游戏之间
between apps and games.
貌似总有种压迫感
And we felt it was a problem we
我们觉得这个问题
needed to solve, as apps are
需要解决
incredibly important and have a
因为应用非常重要
huge impact on how we live our
对我们的生活也有着巨大影响
By splitting games and apps we
游戏和应用分开后
can give both of them the
双方都能获得
attention they deserve.
应得的关注
And finding new apps will be so
有了应用预览后
much easier with App Previews,
找到新应用就容易得多了
as you see in this example for
举个例子
Mammals.
像 Mammals 这样
What you will see in both tabs
在两个标签内都能看到
are in-app purchases.
应用内购买
Up to this point they had a very
之前它们在 App Store 里
limited presence in the App
的出现频率很有限
But we're changing it completely
但现在我们重新设计了
with this redesign.
情况就完全改变了
They will be much more
现在它们
accessible and discoverable
在 App Store 里更显眼
throughout the App Store.
更方便使用
You will see them on the Today
这些都能在 Today 标签中看到
We actually designed a card
我们专门设计了
specifically for in-app
应用内购买的卡片
purchases.
这些卡片在 App 和游戏标签下
Apps and Games tab.
都会被高亮显示
And they will be searchable.
也可以搜索到
They will also be featured by
您也可以在
you on your product pages.
产品页面中推荐卡片
It is a complete story.
这样就完美了
What's probably even more
更重要的是
important, how easy it is to get
现在应用内购买
the in-app purchases, especially
变得十分简单
if you have the app installed on
尤其是当您已经在自己的电子产品上
your own device.
安装了应用之后
I'm going to start with the
我要从
Today tab and the card
Today 标签
specifically designed for the
和专门为应用内购买设计的卡片
in-app purchases.
开始讲起
I'm going to tap on the Buy
我要轻点一下
button.
购买按钮
The app will open.
应用就打开了
And the purchase sheet will come
弹出购买页
up.
然后用 Touch ID 确认
I'm done.
就搞定了
It's simple and direct.
简单又直接
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
When designing the visual
在设计
treatment for in-app purchases,
应用内购买的视觉效果时
it was important to us that
有一点很重要
these wouldn't be confused for
要注意这些不能和
being app icons.
应用图标相混淆
We started with the image that
于是我们从
you will be providing for
你们会为
featuring your in-app purchases.
应用内购买提供的特征图片开始
And we added a framing system
然后添加框架系统
that helps convey what these
来帮助传达信息
truly are, in addition to an app
确定真正指向
or a game.
应用或游戏
And the [inaudible] helps
这个加号
communicate that as well.
也很有用
The curve of the frame actually
边框的曲线
follows the shape of the app
是按照现在 App Store 里
icons on the App Store today.
应用的图标来的
And the way we think of in-app
我们是这样看待应用内购买的
purchases is that they are the
它们是
smaller part of the larger
大整体的小部分
piece, which is the app itself.
大整体即应用本身
It was also still important to
同样重要的是
us to keep that connection
保持
between the in-app purchase and
应用内购买和
the parent app.
母应用之间的联系
So we added the app icon in the
所以我们在
lower left corner, again for
左下角添加了母应用的图标
more context.
同样也提供了更多内容
If you would like to feature
如果您想要
your in-app purchases on a
在商店里突出您的应用内购买
store, you will need to submit
您需要为
an image for every single one of
每一个应用内购买
your in-app purchases.
单独提交一幅图像
It needs to be a custom design
需要定制设计条件
asset that helps describe what
来帮助描述
your in-app purchase is about.
您的应用内购买的具体情况
It should not be a screen shot
单独提交的图像不应是
from your app or an app icon.
应用或应用图标的屏幕快照
The last goal, clarity and
最后一个目标
simplification, is also the most
简明
important, like I mentioned
也是设计里最重要的
earlier, from the design
就像我之前提到的
perspective.
那样
It also had the biggest
对整个重新设计
influence on the entire
影响也最大
When designing our products, we
在设计产品时
constantly ask ourselves: Is
我们常常问自己
this simple enough?
这样够简洁了吗
Is this clear to everyone?
这样够明了了吗
And can we achieve the same goal
我们能不能用更简单的方式
with less?
达到相同的目标
The most significant area of the
对于 App Store 最重要的方面
App Store that probably
大概就是
demonstrates how this goal
说明这个目标
affected our process is the
是如何在产品合集中
Product page.
影响进程的
This is also home for your apps.
这里也是您的应用之家
So I want to spend a little more
所以我想再花点时间
time on it.
讲一讲这方面的内容
Over the years, we've added a
这些年来
lot of different features to
我们一直在向
this page without having the
页面中添加新特色
opportunity to take a step back
却没能有机会退一步
and look at it holistically.
从整体层面看一看
We knew we had to simplify,
我们知道需要简化
especially the top of the page,
尤其是页面顶端部分
as this is what your customers
因为这是用户第一眼
see first.
看到的部分
And all of the relevant
所有相关信息
information had to be clearly
都必须被清晰
communicated.
传达
We wanted to highlight this
我们想突出
app's achievement on the App
应用在 App Store 内的成就
So its star rating, Editor's
所以显示星级评分
Choice and charting position, if
编辑之选和排行榜
available.
如果有的话
We included age rating to this
这部分还包括年龄分级
section, as we know it's
因为我们知道
incredibly important, especially
这一点十分重要
for those of us who are parents.
对家长们尤为如此
All this information had to be
这些信息都需要
quickly scannable and easy to
一目了然
understand.
清晰易懂
Videos and screenshots are still
视频和屏幕快照依然是
the heroes of this page, just
本页面的主角
like they are today.
这一点和现在一样
But now with auto-playing video,
但现在有了自动播放
this page comes to life.
页面就更加生动了
You will also get up to three
之前只有一个视频
videos versus just one.
现在有三个了
And we know that people want to
我们知道人们想看到
engage with beautiful app
精美的应用预览
And we will feature them much
所以我们会在用户界面
more heavily throughout our UI.
更着重推荐这些内容
We redesigned how we communicate
我们也重新设计了交流的方式
if this app is universal.
从应用的整体性出发
This is also how you see screen
这里是从其他设备
shots from the other devices.
看到的屏幕快照
We enjoy apps that have been
我们喜欢
designed and work on all the
设计成能在各种设备
different devices.
都能用的应用
We drastically simplified how we
我们极大地简化了
present ratings and reviews.
评分和评论的呈现方式
They're much easier to read, and
现在易读性更高
their presentation has -- their
呈现方式
graphic presentation has been
即图表形式
refined.
也有所改善
We've removed the All versions
我们移除了所有版本
versus Current version split
和当前版本
between ratings.
评分的分隔
So updating your apps will no
所以今后升级应用
longer hide your ratings the way
不会再隐藏评分了
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
The reviews are really easy to
评论区很好操作
Simply swipe to the left or tap
只需向左滑动
on the CL link.
或轻点CL链接
And we included the Editor's
这部分还有
Choice in this section as well.
编辑之选
So all the reviews are in one
这样一来所有评论
place.
就都在一起了
The information section
信息部分
underwent a makeover as well.
也有所改变
So it's a lot easier to read.
提高了可读性
And we are featuring more apps
我们还在同一页面内
and games by this developer on
推荐这一开发者
this page or any other products
或其他你可能喜欢的
that are related and you might
相关应用
Lastly, it was important to us
最后一点
to make it easy for you as you
用户能顺畅地下拉页面
scroll down the page to download
并下载应用
the app.
也很重要
We love the bar that comes down
我们很喜欢顶端下拉栏
as you absorb the content.
大家在阅读内容的时候可以拉下来
The transition is smooth and the
操作转换十分顺畅
bar is integrated with the
下拉栏也和
overall page design.
整个页面的设计融为一体
And that is the redesigned App
这就是重新设计的 App Store
We worked hard to make the new
为了做出一个
store a place people will love
让人们爱不释手流连忘返的 App Store
and will want to come to every
我们十分努力
day.
也希望你们会认同我们的努力
Next, I want to invite Smokey
下面我想欢迎 Smokey Fontaine
Fontaine to talk to you about
来和大家介绍一下
our editorial strategy for the
新 App Store 的编辑策略
Thank you all for your
谢谢大家
attention.
的聆听
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thank you, Monika.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢 Monika
Thank you, Monika, so much for
谢谢你为我们
showing us that beautiful,
带来如此美秒的
beautiful redesign.
重新设计
My name is Smokey Fontaine.
我的名字是 Smokey Fontaine
And yes, that is my real name.
是的这是我真名
In many ways I'm glad they don't
从很多方面来讲
let me touch the product.
他们不让我接触产品我还挺高兴的
I only get to touch the
我只能摆弄编辑
editorial.
这部分
I am the editorial director here
我是 App Store 的
of the App Store.
编辑主管
It is my great pleasure to
我很高兴
really talk to us about what
能真正讲讲
does "editorial" mean for the
编辑对于 App Store
App Store?
意味着什么
How does original content, how
原始内容
will it bring our customers to
如何用更新颖更令人兴奋的方式
the store in new and exciting
将用户带进商店里呢
And how can our added
我们的更多视角
perspective really transform the
如何将 App Store 从
store from the phenomenal
以往的非凡服务提供端
service and utility it has
转型为
always been to a place where our
用户和顾客
users and our customers can come
能返回至此
back and read, watch, and
阅读内容观看视频
listen, and discover more than
并且聆听和发现
they ever, ever have before.
远超先前的更多内容
Here's what we're going to
我将讲到以下几部分
Our editorial principles.
我们的编辑原则
We have the set of new tabs, as
现在有了一套新标签
you've seen today, games and
就是大家今天看到的游戏和
apps.
App 标签
More options for you.
让您拥有更多选项
And we'll end with the big
最后将以一个大问题作为
question.
结束
Let's start with who we are.
那就先从我们是谁开始吧
Who is the Editorial Team?
编辑团队是谁
Well, first and foremost, we are
首先我们是粉丝
We are fans of all of the work
我们是你们开发者所做工作
that you do.
的粉丝
We really, really love this
我们超爱
stuff.
你们的工作
In fact, I'm standing here right
实际上我现在站在这儿
now without my phone.
没拿手机
And I'm feeling a little lonely.
感觉有点孤独
How many folks have actually
从这场报告开始
used an app since this
有多少人已经
presentation has been on?
用过一个应用了
Anyone? How many people have
有没有
played a game since this
又有多少人已经
presentation has been on?
玩过一场游戏了呢
Anyone? Well, maybe you're even
有没有
making, you're finishing your
说不定你们甚至正在开发过程中
apps and polishing up your games
在我们讲述的同时做完了应用
as we speak.
完善了游戏
And that's what we love to do as
这些也是我们喜欢的
In fact, all of our App Store
实际上
editors around the world wake up
全世界所有 App Store 的编辑们
really excited to try to find
都在欢欣中醒来
that innovative new app that
努力寻找能够
could change someone's life.
改变某人一生的创新应用
Or that exciting game that
或是寻找能吸引玩家的
customers will spend hours and
让其沉迷于其中的
hours and hours playing.
精彩游戏
We care deeply about all the
我们深度关注
recommendations we make.
自己做出的所有推荐
And it is true.
而且这是真的
We play every game we recommend.
我们会亲自试玩我们所推荐的每个游戏
And we use every app that we
同样我们也会亲自试用
recommend.
我们所推荐的每个应用
The redesign is so exciting for
我们对重新设计兴奋不已
us because now we have the
因为这样一来
ability to provide even more
我们就能提供更多内容
context, even more perspective,
更多视角
and in many ways a narrative to
用更多方式
our recommendations.
讲述我们的推荐
So customers can come and find
于是用户进店能找到
everything they want and need
他们所想所需所爱
and love.
的一切
Find all of the work that you
能找到你们创作的所有内容
create.
我们有一套编辑原则
And if you come to our story
如果你来到我们
rooms around the world, and this
在世界各地的故事厅
is not just in Cupertino, but
比如库比蒂诺
this is in London and Tokyo.
伦敦东京
This is in Seoul.
首尔
This is even in Dubai.
甚至迪拜
These editorial principles
编辑原则
really guide the writing that we
指导我们编写的内容
They will guide our creative
引领我们的
process.
创意流程
We start with the first one.
先从第一个讲起
We celebrate apps.
我们赞扬应用
This for us is really our most
对我们来说
important point.
这是最重要的一点
Now that we have a bigger
现在我们的编辑平台更大了
editorial platform, it does not
但这并不意味着
mean that we're going to all of
我们要突然开始
a sudden start reviewing apps.
审查应用
It does not mean that we're
这并不意味着
going to all of a sudden going
我们要突然开始
to start criticizing apps.
批判应用
We are cheer leaders.
我们是啦啦队才对
Unapologetic cheerleaders of
一心只为应用
apps and app culture.
和应用文化喝彩
For us, it's really the most
对我们来说这真的是
creative work in the world.
世界上最具创造性的工作
And that is our number one
这也是我们的
principle.
首要原则
We celebrate apps.
我们赞扬应用
Second is that we are the voice
第二条原则
of the App Store.
我们是 App Store 的发声者
You know, during this redesign
要知道在重新设计期间
we thought long and hard about
我们认真考虑了很久
not only what we're going to
不光是写什么
write, but how we're going to
还有怎么写
It's a big responsibility to be
担任发声者这一角色
that voice.
责任重大
It's a big responsibility to
要面向上亿名用户
kind of be the mouthpiece to
传递 App Store 的声音
hundreds and hundreds of
责任重大
And for that we want to kind of
为了这一点
be authentic to who we are.
我们忠于自我
We want it to be smart and fun.
我们想要聪慧有趣
We want it to be humble, for
想要谦卑
sure.
当然
And very friendly.
还要友好
Hopefully, a lot of our work
希望我们的大多数工作
will be in a kind of
都能有
conversational tone.
交流传达的作用
And of course, we want to be
当然我们也要
passionate about all the stuff.
充满激情
We are going to be very Apple.
我们要充满苹果范儿
We're going to obsess over every
我们要执着于
word, every word, every word, so
每个字每个词
that our customers can -- we can
我们能
help them and engage them as
尽力帮助用户
best as we can.
参与其中
What's our third principle?
那第三条原则呢
Well, we offer independent
就是我们要提供
insights.
独立见解
What's one of the biggest
对于 App Store 而言最大的
criticisms of the App Store?
批判是什么呢
Well, that it's all paid
是付费经营
marketing, right?
对不对
Many of you in this room may
在座的许多人可能
have tried to engage us with
曾努力和我们沟通
suggestions to feature one of
建议推荐你们
your apps or feature one of your
的某个应用或
games.
游戏
And you probably know that money
而且你们大概也知道
isn't the answer to that.
在这儿钱不是解决问题的答案
Well, nothing in the redesigned
其实在重新设计的 App Store 里
App Store on Today Games or Apps
Today 的游戏或 App 里
is advertising.
没有广告宣传
We are strong experts with an
我们是拥有
editorial point of view.
编辑视角的专家
And we are great storytellers
我们是优秀的故事大师
with a personality and with a
有个性
perspective that we want to
有见地
share.
想要和大家分享
Now, why is this important?
为什么这一点很重要呢
We want customers to really
因为我们希望用户能
trust the recommendations that
真正信赖我们的推荐
We want them to be able to rely
能依靠
on what we share with them.
我们的分享做出选择
Why? So they'll ultimately come
为什么呢
back every day and find
因为如此他们才能每天加入进来
tremendous value in the App
并在 App Store 中
Store's editorial.
找到巨大的价值
Fourth. While we wordsmith this
第四当我们这群故事大师讲故事时
a lot, let me tell you.
我得告诉你这些
We tell interesting and
我们讲的故事既有趣
important stories.
又重要
First it was, "We tell
最开始时
interesting stories."
我们讲述有趣的故事
Then it was, "We tell insanely
然后变成
And this is where we landed,
现在我们到达了目的地
"Interesting and important
要讲既有趣又重要
stories."
的故事
Now, for sure, not every single
现在可以肯定的是
story on Today is going to be
并不是 Today 中的每一个故事
super, super important.
都超级重要
But we're going to try really,
但我们会加倍努力
really hard to make sure that
来确保
they are very interesting.
它们十分有趣
They key for us is that us being
关键在于
able to say that this app is
我们说
great is no longer enough.
这个应用很厉害已经远远不够了
In the current app store, that's
在当前的 App Store 里
what we say.
我们是这样说的没错
And we feature and promote those
而且我们推荐这些
apps.
应用
In our new design, newly
在新设计中
designed App Store, we will say
也就是新设计的 App Store 中
that app is great, but then
我们会说这个应用很厉害
explain why we believe it is to
然后向用户说明
our customers.
为什么我们这样认为
We're here to provide
我们在此
thought-provoking ideas and
提供发人深省的观点
really offer that context.
和语境内容
Our fifth and last principle is
第五也就是最后一条原则
we deliver a fresh and
我们传达一种清新的
unexpected take.
意想不到的观点
You know, the world of apps is
大家都知道
moving at a ridiculous speed.
应用的世界正在飞速向前
It is our job, we believe, to
而我们相信
reflect that innovative culture.
反映这种创新文化是我们的本职
You guys are pushing the world
你们推动世界
ahead.
前行
All of you are shaping our lives
用你们的创造
with what you create.
塑造我们的生活
And often you've changed things
而且常有这种情况
in ways that are totally
各位凭借让人意想不到的方式
unexpected.
改变了世界
So, we want to try to keep up
所以我们想和你们
with you.
保持步调一致
Keep up with that speed.
跟上你们的节奏
And for us, we kind of call this
对我们来说我们把这叫做
our "the crazy ones" principles.
疯狂的原则
A fresh and unexpected take.
清新而独特的观点
So these five principles all
所以把这五大原则放在一起
together: We celebrate apps.
赞扬应用
We are the voice of the App
做 App Store 的发声者
We offer independent insights.
提供独立见解
We tell interesting and
讲述有趣
important stories.
又重要的故事
And we deliver a fresh and
传达清新的
unexpected take.
又独特的观点
When we do all this, if around
当我们这样做时
the world we abide by these
如果在世界各地
principles, then hopefully the
都遵循这些原则
Today tab and the whole new App
那就希望 Today 标签和全新的 App Store
Store become a pretty fabulous
能成为应用文化里
document of app culture.
非凡的篇章
And for us at the App Store, app
对于我们 App Store 人来说
culture in almost every single
应用文化
way is culture.
几乎方方面面皆成文化
All right.
好的
The new tabs: Today, Games, and
新标签
Apps.
Today、游戏和 App
Each of these tabs have the same
每个标签都有相同的
goal.
目标
But we approach them
但实现目标的方式
differently.
有所不同
Today, well, Today is going to
Today 标签
be updated every day.
是要每日更新的
Don't really have a choice
这没什么好选择的
there.
所以起了这个名字
It's going to have a very
焦点关注
It's going to be highly
与语境高度相关
And when customers tap on cards
用户轻点 Today 标签里的卡片时
in Today, they can actually go
就可以直接
directly to buy that app or game
从卡片中
from the card.
购买应用或游戏
Or of course, tap in and read
当然了也可以轻点一下
one of our stories.
阅读其中一个故事
The Games and Apps tabs are
游戏和 App 标签
going to be different.
会有很大不同
In many ways you can think about
从许多方面来看你可以把它看作
those as a 2.0 version or a
现有主题标签的
newly evolved version of the
2.0版
Feature tab now, including
或是全新升级版
categories and including charts,
包括类别和排行榜
as you're seeing.
正如你所看到的那样
Well, the Games and Apps tabs
游戏和 App 标签
are going to be updated often.
会经常更新
Not every day.
但不是每天
But more often than the weekly
现在是每周进行更新
that you see in today's cadence.
以后肯定会比这个频繁
Games and Apps are going to
游戏和 App
offer a broader selection.
也会有更多选择
And it's generally going to be a
总体体验的
more transactional experience.
交互性更强
Taps on Games and Apps will take
轻点游戏和 App
customers directly to our
会直接进入
amazing new product pages.
令人惊艳的全新产品页面
Well, let me chat a little bit
下面让我来介绍一下
about what we call our Story
我们称之为
Framework.
故事框架的东西
As you're seeing, stories on the
如各位所见
App Store will cover many, many
App Store 里的故事涵盖
things.
很多内容
We'll have world premieres.
我们有世界最佳
We'll have major updates.
有主要更新
We'll have tips and tricks and
有自己的小技巧
interviews with developers and
有和开发者的访谈
lists upon lists.
还有成堆的榜单
Well, our job is to write about
我们的工作
what we think customers will
就是找到在我们看来
find most interesting about an
用户会在应用或游戏上看到的
app or a game.
最有趣的闪光点
And we really believe every app
我们坚信
has a story to tell.
每个应用都有故事
There are four main topics of
而我们讲故事
stories for us.
遵从四大主题
When we think about all the
我们认为
range, the broad, broad range of
自己拥有
ideas that we have, we try to
那么多观点
make -- we needed to make sense
我们必须
of that.
言之有理才行
So we started with just an idea
所以我们
of topics.
其中一个主题开始介绍
What are the four main topics
四大主题
that we will cover?
是哪四大呢
And for each topic we kind of
对每个主题
have a statement of belief.
我们都有一个信仰声明
This is something that we really
在我们创作书写的内容中
want to have customers feel in
有一些东西
the writing and the content that
我们真的很想让用户感受到
Our first topic is, of course,
第一个主题毫无疑问是
gaming.
玩游戏
Whether it's a big name game or
无论是名声在外的大型游戏
a small indie who has a
还是名不见经传的独立游戏
car-based strategy, RPG,
无论是汽车主题策略
Infinite Runner, it doesn't
角色扮演游戏
matter.
还是无限跑酷都没关系
The games you make are so
你们创作的游戏
innovative and so creative, our
创意非凡
game editors really believe
我们的游戏编辑都深信不疑
that, you know what?
你知道吗
Apps are the future of gaming.
应用是游戏的未来
In many ways apps are the
从很多角度来看
present of gaming.
应用都是游戏的现在时
Anyone agree with that comment?
有没有人同意这一点
Apps are the present of gaming?
应用是游戏的现在时
Hey, we do have the biggest
而我们确实有
gaming platform in the world.
全世界最大的游戏平台
And you know, we're very
如诸位所知
enthusiastic about expressing to
我们会热情的向用户传达
our customers what we believe
信仰
the future is in games.
未来就在游戏中
Our second topic: Lifestyle.
第二个主题是生活方式
Well, what do we believe there?
我们的信仰是什么呢
Apps transform your life.
应用改变生活
Whether it's social networking
不管是社交
or photography.
还是摄影
Whether it's dating or fitness
约会还是健身
or cooking or transportation,
下厨还是通勤
apps have helped us live in ways
应用都以
that we've never, ever, ever
意想不到的方式
thought possible.
为我们的生活带来方便
And we believe in our lifestyle
所以我们相信
coverage that apps transform
就生活方式而言
your life.
应用改变生活
Third, culture and
第三
entertainment.
文娱
Apps shape culture.
应用塑造文化
Well, this is music, film,
音乐电影
fashion.
时尚
This is TV, pop culture and
电视流行文化
everything in between.
之间所有种种
The App Store is going to bring
App Store 要将它们
all that together.
都集合起来
And so App Store [inaudible]
所以 App Store 的核心内容
content may talk to celebrities.
可能要与名人对话
We may talk to influencers.
与有影响力的人对话
We may talk to culture creators
与文化创造者对话
of all kinds about the world of
交流
apps and games because we
应用和游戏的世界
believe apps really do shape
因为我们相信
culture.
应用确实塑造着文化
And our fourth and final topic
第四个也就是最后一个主题
is, of course, new tech and
即
innovation.
新技术与创新
This is all things new, new,
这里的一切都是
new.
新的
New services.
新服务
New ideas.
新观点
New capabilities.
新能力
Completely new ways of getting
是使用 iPhone 与 iPad
things done with your iPhone or
完成任务的全新方式
And we really feel that we can
我们切实感觉到
provide a service to customers
我们能够提供一种服务
to help them figure it all out.
帮助用户去解决问题
Help them get great use out of
帮助他们
all the innovative work that you
最大化的挖掘你们
do.
的创作
And help them potentially be
帮助他们
introduced into a whole new way
打开全新做事方法
of doing things.
的潜在途径
In many ways it's very Apple of
在很多方面这都十分的苹果范儿
us.
我们想把复杂的科技世界
world of technology simple.
变得简单
All right.
好嘞
Four topics: Gaming, lifestyle,
四大主题玩游戏生活方式
culture and entertainment, and
文娱和
new tech and innovation.
新技术与创新
When we take these topics, and
当我们拿到这些主题时
once we've decided on one, then
一旦决定
we want to apply what we call an
我们就要用到
"intention."
意图
And this is essentially the
本质上讲
purpose or the goal of each
就是 App Store 里
story that you will see on the
每一个你将看到的故事的
App Store.
目的或目标
There are three of those.
意图有三
The first we call "Inform."
其一我们称为告知
This is about being timely.
要及时
This is about giving customers
告诉用户
"need-to-know" information.
他们需要知道的信息
This is to obviously let them
也就是让他们知道
know what's happening in the
世界上正在发生
world right now.
的事情
For example, you can say a new
举个例子 Netflix 上
show is launching on Netflix.
播出了新剧
And if we do that well, our
如果我们做得不错
customer reaction may very
用户的反应很可能是
likely be: "Cool.
酷啊
I want to get that."
这个我想要
Our second intention is simply
其二很简单
called "Help."
就是帮助
Really, really important for us.
对我们非常重要
This is about being
要指导
This is about sharing ideas that
要分享想法
may be intuitive for us but not
可能对我们直观易懂
for all of our customers.
但对其他用户并非如此
How to get the most out of
如何将 Instagram 的新功能
Instagram's new feature could be
最大化
a helpful topic.
这是个实用性主题
And for us, this can be a really
对我们而言这也是种
helpful way of reengaging our
帮助用户重温
customers with some apps that
应用的有效方式
they may have downloaded, may
可能之前下载了
knew they loved them, but
也喜欢了一段时间
they've been left idle.
然后就闲置一旁
So how can we reengage our
那么我们要如何
customers with some of those
让用户重温
apps and even games by helping
应用或者游戏
them, giving them new ideas of
给予他们全新的动力
how to use one of these great
来好好使用这些软件
And third, it's "Inspire."
其三为启发
This is going to be the topic
这一主题
area or the intention where we
或意图
have really creative content,
集中了极具创意
really motivational content,
鼓舞人心
really insightful.
见地独到的内容
This is going to be everything
涵盖了
from a twelve-year-old making an
从12岁的开发者
app to the 82-year-old making an
到82岁的开发者所做的内容
app, both of whom were here this
而这二位今年都来到了大会现场
This is inspiring content that
启发性内容
may go global around the world.
可能会走向全世界
Inform, help and inspire.
告知帮助启发
If we inform, "Cool.
如果我们告知内容
I want to get that."
酷啊这个我想要
If we help, "I had no idea.
如果我们帮到了用户
Thanks." And if we inspire,
本来没头绪的多谢啦
"Wow!
如果我们启发他人
That's super interesting."
哇简直太有趣了
And of course, we are not going
当然我们不会
to count any of those reactions
细数这些反应
unless customers use those exact
除非用户把上述语句
phrases on the screen.
敲到屏幕上
Let's see how this all comes
那咱们来看看
together.
这些都是怎样聚合在一起的
All right.
好
Our first world premiere ever,
我们的第一个世界最佳是
ever, ever is "The Art of the
不可能的艺术
Inside the extraordinary world
在纪念碑谷 2
of Monument Valley 2."
的非凡世界里
Well, why did we choose this?
为什么我们选了它呢
First and foremost, it comes
首先
back to our first principle,
回到我们的第一条原则上
which was Monument Valley 2 is
纪念碑谷 2
an awesome, awesome game.
是一款非常非常出色的游戏
How many folks have tried it so
到现在为止有多少人玩过它呢
Since Monday release.
自从周一发布之后
I can say I have not even got
我得说
very far.
我还没玩太久
But it's a phenomenal,
但真的是
phenomenal game.
无与伦比的一款游戏
And Ustwo did a great job with
Ustwo 做得实在是太漂亮了
this.
所以首先
Monument Valley 2 as our world
我们选择纪念碑谷 2 作为
premiere because the game is
世界最佳是因为
flat our awesome.
这游戏真的棒到不行
Secondly, the Ustwo team gave us
其次  Ustwo 团队给了我们
great access to their
不少访问权限
development process.
让我们得以接触到开发流程
They allowed us in and we got to
这样我们就能
meet with some of their
认识他们团队中的
creatives and speak to some of
一些创作人员
their art directors about what
并和艺术主管交谈
inspired them to make Monument
是什么启发了他们
Valley 2.
制作纪念碑谷 2
That was really interesting and
这对我们来说
exciting for us because we knew
十分有趣而且激动人心
we could tell that story, then,
因为我们知道
to customers.
随后我们可以把这个故事讲给玩家听
And thirdly, we knew we had a
再次我们知道
great story for customers about
有了纪念碑谷 2 的好故事
Monument Valley 2.
可以介绍给玩家
And of course it helped that it
当然这款游戏只在 iOS 平台发布
was only available on iOS.
也是帮了很大的忙
All right.
好
There's a moment in the third
在纪念碑谷 2 里
stage of Monument Valley 2 when
第三关有这样一个情节
a landslide separates mother
山体滑坡将母子俩
from child.
分离
I actually did get to this
我还真玩到这儿了
To get her little one back, mom
为了母子团圆
must navigate through intricate,
母亲必须小心地解开复杂
artfully-crafted puzzle that
巧妙而又
constantly evolves.
变化多端的谜题
There was an actual moment, I
真的有那么一刻
got to it later, but one of our
我后来才玩到
game editors, this really
但有一位游戏编辑
happened to him.
他被那一瞬间触动了
He was playing and it's like "Oh
他当时正在玩
my God.
然后感慨了一句我的天啊
It was such an awesome moment."
这瞬间太美妙了
Then they embrace after.
然后母子相拥
And it really kind of moved him.
这一情景感动了他
And we said, "You know what?
于是我们就说定了
That's the intro to our Monument
这就是我们给
Valley 2 story."
纪念碑谷 2 的故事简介了
We've seen some of the beautiful
我们见到了一部分美丽的设计
We've seen how the copy flows in
也见到了美妙的画面
between these great images and
穿行其中
in-line video.
还看到了在线视频
And of course, we have pull
当然也有醒目格言
quotes.
醒目格言不是苹果的发明创造
but it's really nice to see them
但在 App Store 里看到
on the App Store.
还是挺不错的
Here we quoted us to studio head
我们在这儿引用了工作室领导
Dan Gray, who wants to change
Dan Gray 的名言
people's perceptions of what
他想改变人们对游戏的看法
That's our first world premiere
这就是我们的首个世界最佳了
of Monument Valley 2.
纪念碑谷 2
Here is our first How To column.
这里是我们的第一个如何栏
Monika spoke about a little bit
刚才 Monika 讲了一点
earlier.
其实啊
And you know what?
有很多方式
could have spoken about VSCO.
可以讲讲 VSCO 的
It's one of our favorite apps
它是我们最喜欢的应用之一
and one of our favorite photo
也是我们最喜欢的
filter apps for a long, long
滤镜应用之一
time.
很久以来一直都是
And here we wanted to -- we felt
所以我们想
the most helpful angle would be
我们觉得最有帮助的角度应该是
kind of a basic primer of some
从最初级的
of the new features of VSCO that
一些 VSCO 的新特色讲起
many customers may not have used
这些功能用户可能还没用过
Well, let's look at some of
下面咱们来看一看
them.
这些功能
Don't fall on stage.
别摔到舞台上
Like a good denim jacket -- it's
像优质牛仔夹克一样
funny, we had this image.
我们刚好有这张图
It was initially the phrase is
最初这句话是
often "like a good leather
像优质皮夹克一样
We changed it to "like a good
我们把它改成了
denim jacket."
像优质牛仔夹克一样
How many people love the denim
有多少人喜欢
jacket that we gave out WWDC
今年我们在 WWDC 大会
Swag this year?
发出去的牛仔夹克
So I'm glad, actually.
其实我挺高兴的
Round of applause for the denim
掌声献给
jackets.
牛仔夹克
[ Applause ]
[掌声]
Well here you are right here.
现在各位都在这儿了
Like a good denim jacket.
就像优质牛仔夹克一样
VSCO's got a coolness factor
VSCO 有一种
that can't be measured.
无法言表的高冷气质
All right, we wanted to talk
然后我们想谈谈
about creating gifts.
创建礼物
Many folks don't know that you
许多人不知道
can create gifts in VSCO.
能用 VSCO 来创建礼物
It's a feature that many users,
这一功能获得了很多用户的推崇
both amateur and pro, love to
有菜鸟也有行家
That was number one.
这是第一点
We go now, we can make journals
再往下看
of VSCO.
还能用 VSCO 生成日志
We talk about some of their free
这里还有一些免费
filters.
滤镜
And of course, we end here with
当然最后
the kind of hidden, if you will,
如果你发现了它的隐藏功能
social network that's within
VSCO 里还可以社交
Tip number five, you can
第五条小贴士
socialize without having to go
无需出门
anywhere else.
即可社交
So this was our first How To
这也就是我们的第一个
story.
如何做的故事
This is very interesting because
这是件趣事
one of the biggest challenges
因为 App Store 编辑团队
about App Store Editorial is how
面临的最大挑战就是如何
can we serve a billion people
用独到的见解
with perspective?
为十亿人服务
That's really, really, really
真是好难好难
Well, you have to figure out
首先要想清楚
first who you want to speak to.
要和谁交流
And it's as important to us on
对于App Store的我们来说
the App Store to talk to new
和新用户交流
users as it is to talk to
与和高阶用户交流
advanced users.
同样重要
So this is column is more for an
这一栏更适用于
advanced user.
高阶用户
We call this a Deep Dive.
我们叫它深潜
Here's it's a conversation about
有段关于因果关系的小对话
One of my game editors was
团队里有位游戏编辑
really excited when he got to
他打到201层的时候可激动了
level 201 because everything
因为到了201层
changes on level 201.
一切都变了
You want to feel like a genius,
你要是想拥有天才般的感觉
well, you better get there
最好先打到那一关
first.
这就是
great game in a kind of deeper
有深层次意义的好游戏
We talk about culture and
下面来讲讲
entertainment, all right?
文化和娱乐吧
It's the NBA finals.
现在正是NBA总决赛
We know that game is on tonight.
我们知道就在今晚
Go Warriors!
勇士队加油
I better not say anything else
在加州圣荷斯
in San Jose, California.
我最好别说别的
Go Warriors.
勇士队必胜
And when you look at culture and
当透过应用的镜头
entertainment through the lens
观看文娱时
of apps, there are two actual
有两种方式
ways that you can enjoy it.
让你享受其中
Of course, you can watch the
当然你也可以
game live anywhere you are on
直接在 ESPN 上看直播
But you can also play the game
但你同样可以选择
on NBA Live.
在NBA Live上实时参与
And you can imitate Steph Curry
而且还能模仿库里
or LeBron or whoever you'd like
或者勒布朗喜欢谁就模仿谁
to be on the game itself.
直接参与到比赛当中
In many ways the game is
在许多方面
probably going to be as good as
游戏估计会和比赛一样精彩
-- the video game is going to
因为游戏
imitate the real-life game and
模拟比赛
back and forth, seeing how these
看着这些球员
players are breaking all these
如何打破纪录
So that's our culture and
这就是我们的
entertainment story.
文娱故事
A couple of examples.
举了几个例子
If there's one thing this
如果有一件事
morning I love all of you to
是我希望今天大会结束之后
leave here and remember about
能留在各位记忆中的
the all new App Store is that
那就是新的 App Store 中
there are more ways to be
有比以往更加丰富的方式
featured than ever, ever before.
来实施推荐
We talked about "Meet the
我们说了
Developer."
开发者面对面
Well, yes.
是的没错
You can get interviewed.
会有和大家的访谈
Our debut "Meet the Developer"
我们的首场开发者面对面
piece featured Michelle Kennedy,
嘉宾是 Michelle Kennedy
the creator of a wonderful new
她创作了一款
social media app called Peanut,
名为花生（ Peanut ）的社交软件
which is dedicated to moms.
是为妈妈们设计的
It's our "Meet the Developer"
这是我们的
column.
开发者面对面专栏
We talked to her about many
我们和她聊了很多
things, about her UI and some of
包括她的用户界面
the feature innovations.
以及一些特色创意
And we talked to her about some
我们还聊了
of the feedback she's received
她收到的一些反馈
from her Peanut social media app
反馈来自花生应用
and who it's for.
和应用的目标群体
So we're really excited to have
所以我们真的很高兴
a kind of deeper cultural
能有更深层的文化交流
conversation about an app that's
交流一个应用
really meaningful to a lot of
对于很多人而言都将大有裨益
"Peanut is human interaction in
花生是实际生活中的人际互动
real life, facilitated by
科技使这些变得简单
technology," Michelle said.
Michelle说
Another way you can get featured
另一个获得推荐的方式
is, of course, App of the Day.
当然就是 App 今日亮点了
Here we chose Hit List.
我们从这儿选择热榜
Game of the Day, Super Senso.
游戏今日亮点 Super Senso （超感）
Strategic sci-fi combat.
战略科幻搏斗游戏
Let me pause for a second and
我插一句
talk about App of the Day and
说说 App 今日亮点
Game of the Day.
和游戏今日亮点
We still have Editor's Choice
当然我们保留了
for sure.
编辑推荐
In fact, Editor's Choice is now
其实编辑推荐
a badge on our new product
现在是新产品页面上的一枚徽章
App of the Day and Game of the
App 今日亮点和游戏今日亮点
Day give us a third option of
让我们拥有第三种
really honoring all the great
由衷赞美各位优秀创作
work you do.
的方式
Think of Editor's Choice like
编辑推荐就好比是
our Oscars.
我们的奥斯卡
Like our Best Picture, if you
如果你愿意
will.
也可以看做是最佳画面奖
App of the Day and Game of the
App 今日亮点和游戏今日亮点
Day are going to be similarly
在质量方面会很相似
high quality, super awesome
都是高品质极优秀的应用
apps, but they'll also be pegged
但同时也会
to a story that we may want to
与我们要讲的故事挂钩
Another way to be featured is
另一获得推荐的方式是
Collections.
合辑
Collections are going to be on
合辑将出现在
the Games and Apps tab.
游戏和 App 标签中
They are also going to be here
它们也将同样在 Today 标签中出现
on Today with a cool new design.
配有全新设计
You will see here that Heroes,
在这儿能看到 Heroes （英雄）
what we call Heroes on the Apps
在 App 标签下我们称其为英雄
tab.
还有爱彼迎
rediscover this.
去重新发现这些
And we have Injustice 2 as a new
此外在游戏标签下
game in the Games tab.
有新游戏 Injustice 2 （不义联盟2）
Another way to be featured is
还有一种获得推荐的方式
lists, lists and more lists.
那就是榜单榜单榜单
Our debut one is "15 Inspired
我们的首份榜单是
Indie Games."
15 款灵感独立游戏
Customers irrespective of the
不管媒体怎么看
media love lists.
用户都超爱榜单
And we love them as well on the
我们也超爱榜单
App Store as well.
App Store 里的榜单
All right.
好的
This brings us to the end.
这就要讲到尾声了
The big, big question.
结束之前的大问题
I hope you've enjoyed our kind
我希望大家喜欢
of editorial vision.
我们的编辑视角
It really is a marriage of
这简直是一场
expert curation with this idea
专家操作和美妙观点的联姻
of engaging stories and content
把故事和内容
for our customers.
带给用户
But really all we want to know
但我们想知道的是
is this: How do you reach us?
你们如何联络我们
Well, I'm happy to announce, and
我很高兴地宣布
many of you, many have already
尽管在座的许多人
seen it.
已经看到了
But I'm happy to announce that
但我还是要高兴地宣布
on AppStore.com/promote, that
在 AppStore.com/promote 这里
will redirect to the new
会转到新的
Developer page where not only
开发者页面
will we ask you about your app
我们不只会询问
and your game and the features
关于您的应用游戏推荐
and what's cool about it.
以及它们的闪光点在哪
We'll also have a new area where
我们还增加了一块新区域
it says, "Tell us your story."
上面写着讲出您的故事
We're really, really excited to
我们真的很期待
hear all of the stories you have
能收到您要与我们
to share with us about your
分享有关创作的故事
creative process and what you
以及
want to share with your
您想讲给用户的
customers about apps and games.
关于应用和游戏的故事
So thank you so much.
谢谢大家
We're really excited to be on
非常高兴
this journey together.
能与君同行
Thank you so much.
非常感谢
I'd like now to bring back Mr.
现在我想请出
Pedraum Pardehpoosh to bring us
Pedraum Pardehpoosh 先生
home.
来为我们收场
&gt;&gt; Thanks, Smokey.
&gt;&gt; 谢谢你 Smokey
So you heard some insights into
大家听到了
the why we did this redesign
由设计主管讲述的
from the lead designer herself.
为什么进行重新设计原因
This is a pretty special thing.
观点十分独特
And you heard the insights from
也听到了
Smokey about our doubling down
Smokey所介绍的
on editorial.
编辑团队付出的努力
And got contact information for
同时知晓了
how to get in touch with the
编辑团队
Editorial Team.
的联系方式
This is the dawn of a new day, I
我觉得可以说是
think it's safe to say.
迎来了新一天的曙光
But let's not lose sight of the
但我们也不要忽视了这一点
fact that ultimately all of
最终
these efforts are meant to
所有这些努力
improve the discoverability of
都是为了方便发现
apps and games on the App Store.
App Store 中的应用和游戏
By giving people a reason to
给人们一个
come back to the App Store every
每天打开 App Store 的理由
day and giving the context of
告诉他们
why we're making the
我们做出这些选择
recommendations that we are.
是出于什么原因
This redesign is more than just
本次重新设计不仅仅是
a facelift.
一场翻新
It's created new opportunities
重新设计创造出前所未有的
to get discovered that haven't
新机遇
existed before.
去探索去发现
Whether it's being included in
不管在不在
one of the stories that Smokey
Smokey描绘的故事里
outlined or appearing in the new
有没有出现在
Apps and Games tabs, which give
新的 App 和游戏标签下
focus to each of those areas.
App 和游戏标签将重点放在对应领域下
But as always, you shouldn't
但和之前一样
just rely on being featured by
不能只寄希望于
the App Store to improve your
App Store 推荐
app discovery.
来提升您的应用热度
There's things you can do even
您现在就可以开始
starting now to get ready for
着手准备
the new App Store.
迎接新的 App Store 到来
And we're going to talk just a
关于新的 App Store
couple minutes about them.
我还要讲几句
The first thing is in-app
首先是应用内购买
By way of quick review, in-app
通过快速审查
purchases now have a presence on
应用内购买现在
the App Store.
在 App Store 中出现了
They can appear on the product
应用内购买可以出现在
details page.
产品详情页
In featured content areas.
推荐内容区
In search results.
搜索结果中
And on your product page, excuse
还有您的产品页面
me.
抱歉
This new ability combined with
这一新功能和
the new Subscriptions features
去年宣布推出的订阅功能
that we announced last year,
相结合
giving you brand new
为您提供
opportunities for creating
打造商业可持续发展
sustainable businesses.
的机会
So you'll want to start thinking
各位会想要开始思索
now about the title of these
从现在开始
in-app purchases and the
思索应用内购买的标题
description and the image that
以及关于它们的
you're going to use for them,
描述和图像
particularly now that they have
尤其是现在
such increased visibility.
它们的可视性大大提高
There's a couple of StoreKit
后续还有几场
sessions and an iTunes Connect
StoreKit 分会以及
session where you can get more
iTunes Connect 分会
information about this.
您可以从那儿获取更多信息
We'll review those at the end.
我们将在会议的最后重新回顾一下这些
Titles are now 30 characters in
标题长度
the App Store, in the all new
在全新的 App Store 中
App Store.
被限制为30个字符
But in addition, you will have a
但您会额外获得一个
subtitle.
副标题
Monika showed this in context as
Monika 也讲到了这些
You'll want to think carefully
如何使用副标题
about how to use this subtitle
来传达您的应用信息
to convey what your app does.
您需要三思
To give a little bit more
如何囊括
information about it.
更多信息
To say something compelling.
如何引人入胜
But don't be misleading.
但不能让人误入歧途
Consider using your subtitle to
把使用副标题看成
highlight a feature or a typical
凸显特色
use of your app that'll resonate
或典型用途的方式
with your audience.
能引起用户共鸣
And this subtitle will follow
副标题将
your app title around throughout
符合应用标题的要求
the app store, whether it's in
在整个 App Store 中都是如此
the Apps or the Games tab, on a
不论是在应用中
product page or in search
还是在游戏标签下产品页面里
results.
还是在搜索结果中
Let's talk about video app
接下来我们来谈谈
previews.
应用预览视频
We know that when customers
我们知道
engage with these video app
如果用户看了预览视频
previews, customers tend to
他们会更倾向于
download that app or game more.
下载这款应用或游戏
And so we thought about, "Well,
因此我们就想
how can we make it more obvious
怎样才能把这些视频
that these are videos?"
做得更醒目
Well, auto-playing is one way
自动播放
you can do that.
是方法之一
And so we really encourage you,
我们也鼓励您这样做
particularly now that you can
尤其是现在
have three of them.
可以放三个视频
And they can be localized.
还可以做到本地化
You should really be thinking
您应该考虑
about how to create a video that
如何创作
encourages customers to download
能吸引用户下载
your app or game.
您的应用或游戏的视频
We think video is a big deal on
我们觉得
the App Store.
视频在 App Store 中很重要
You can learn more about what
您可以通过访问网站
makes a compelling video by
和参观 App Store 实验室
visiting the site, and by
来了解更多
visiting the App Store labs.
如何制作扣人心弦的视频的信息
Now, in addition to your app
现在除了应用介绍外
description, you can have 170
您还有 170 字符长度的
characters of text, which can be
文本
updated any time.
可以随时更新
We call this Promo Text.
我们把它称作广告文本（ Promo Text ）
This will get concatenated on
它将出现在
top of your app description.
您的应用介绍的顶端
And it won't require an app
而且无需
update.
更新应用
This is a great way to talk
这种方式很好
about one of the new features
用来介绍新特色
that's a temporary feature or a
不论是暂时功能
price promotion that you're
还是降价促销
having or some new accolade that
还是您的应用
your app has received.
新获得的嘉奖
This is something else that you
这些是
can start thinking about right
您可以现在就
now.
开始考虑的部分
Let's talk about ratings and
我们来看一下评分
reviews.
和评论
This got some applause.
它们赢得了不少掌声
This warms my heart.
看得我心里暖洋洋的
We did a couple things in iOS
在 iOS 10.3 系统中
10.3 releasing a Reviews API.
我们发布了评论 API （应用程序界面）
And allowing developers to
让开发者能够
respond to reviews.
回复评论
And the response has been
回应简直
tremendous.
多到惊人
We've seen almost 400,000 --
我们看了大约4百万条
this number's actually a little
这儿显示的数据
old.
有点旧了
We've seen almost 400,000
我们看到了大约4百万条
responses to reviews since the
回复
launch of this.
从发布到现在
And we know that when customers
而且我们知道
go back and change their rating
如果有用户
based on a response that they
在收到开发者回复之后
have received from a developer,
去修改评论
overwhelmingly that change in
几乎都是
direction is in a positive way.
把评论往好了改
So this is really important.
所以这一点十分重要
In the new App Store, as Monika
在新 App Store 中
mentioned, we no longer reset
像 Monika 说的那样
app rating when you submit a new
当您提交新版本时
version.
我们不会再重置应用评分
Which is awesome for many
这对许多开发者来说
developers.
都是好消息
Some developers wouldn't mind
有些开发者可能不介意
resetting that rating.
重置评分
And now, with the new App Store,
现在有了新的 App Store
with each submission you're
每次提交新应用时
going to have the ability to do
您都可以
so, to reset your rating.
重置评分
But you should be careful about
但您要谨慎
that.
因为这听起来
option.
挺有趣
But we know that customers value
但我们知道
that rating or seeing that an
用户很看重
app has ratings, a lot, when
应用的评分
they're making a download
尤其是考虑
decision.
下载应用时
So you will want to be careful
所以您还是需要
about that.
三思而后行
You can get advice about best
您可以通过
practices associated with
访问这个网址
responding to customer reviews
来获得有关用户评论回应
by visiting this URL.
的信息
And like we mentioned, we
正如之前提到的那样
strongly recommend you make
我们强烈建议
responding to customer reviews a
您将回复用户评论
regular part of your customer
作为日常服务
service hygiene.
的一部分
And in fact, in July, in iTunes
实际上在7月时
Connect, we'll be enabling a new
我们会在 iTunes Connect 上
role in iTunes Connect for
增加新功能
customer service so that you can
这样您就能让
have somebody that's focused
专人负责
just on that and doesn't have
只负责这一部分
access to other elements inside
而对其他部分没有访问权限
We're constantly improving the
我们一直在努力提升
way Core Search works in the
App Store 中
Apps Store.
Core Search （核心搜索）的功能
But the most visible thing we've
但今年我们做的最明显的变动
done this year is by adding the
是添加了
stories that our editors are
编辑写出的故事
Additionally, in-app purchases,
除此之外应用内购买
categories and developers will
类别和开发者
be able to appear in these
将都能出现在
search results as well.
搜索结果中
Speaking of search, last year we
说到搜索
announced Search Ads.
去年我们宣布了 Search Ads （搜索广告）
And it launched in the US.
并在美国进行了发布
And it launched in the UK,
今年4月在英国
Australia and New Zealand in
澳大利亚和新西兰
April.
进行了发布
The results have been really
在广告发布商中
strong for advertisers.
反响热烈
High tap through rates.
从数据上能看到点击
Conversion rates above 50%.
转化率达到50%
And cost per acquisition just
CPA 超过
over a dollar.
1美元
These are really impressive
这对于广告人员来说
numbers for those that know
是很可观的数据了
An apps flyer industry study
在今年早些时候
published earlier this year
有一份应用传单行业研究
described the quality of users
里面提到使用 Search Ads 的
Search Ads delivers were the
用户质量是
best 30-day retention rate for
iOS 应用30日保留率最高的
iOS apps and a top three ranking
在游戏方面也
for games.
跻身前三
We're working hard to deliver
我们十分努力
opportunities to drive downloads
创造机会
and engagement with your apps.
为你们应用增加下载和用户参与
And bringing Search Ads to more
并将 Search Ads 带到
of the markets that you've told
更多之前你们告诉我们的
us are important to your
对开发者商业
business.
很重要的市场
Many developers large and small
许多大大小小的开发者
have already taken advantage of
都已经在利用了这一点
it.
这也是另一件
want to consult with us about to
您要和我们商量一下
find out if it's right for you.
确定是否于您有益的事
In summary, there's plenty for
简而言之
you to be thinking about even
即便在 iOS 11 发布之前
now in advance of iOS 11
各位也有很多要考虑的事
shipping as it relates to your
因为新系统会影响到
app's presence in the Apps.
您的应用在 App Store 中的状态
And we hope you take advantage
我们希望您能抓住机会
of the folks that are here from
从 App Store 工作者身上
the App Store this week to learn
了解更多
more about this.
正好这周他们都在这里
For more information on this
关于本场会议的更多信息
session you can visit this site.
请访问这个网址
There are related sessions
表中列出了相关会议
listed as well as labs.
还有实验室
Come speak with us.
欢迎来和我们沟通
Last thing I want to say is that
我想说的最后一件事是
it was my honor to be able to
非常荣幸能站在这里
introduce this new App Store
向大家介绍新的 App Store
that's been a few years in the
经历了数年的洗礼
But it was done with a lot of
在多方的努力之下
cross-functional work.
取得了良好的成绩
I know some of those folks in
我知道有些人
the audience today.
今天就坐在台下
Those that work in the App Store
App Store 的工作者们
please stand up for a second to
请站起来
get recognized.
让大家认识一下
Give it up for these folks who
我们为这些
have been working their butts
拼命工作的人
off.
鼓鼓掌吧
[ Applause ]
[掌声]